Lo siento, Gina.
Just to clarify.
Don't get me wrong, brother.
I'm looking out for you here.
You just can't
keep shooting
blanks forever.
I'm sorry.
But trust me, I know
what I'm talking about.
Henry, do you also use
a rifle with a laser sight?
It sounds like an accusation.
Don't dodge the questions.
Just answer about
the fucking rifle.
Enough!
Let Gina speak.
Is it true,
that you can't have children?
Yes.
It is true.
I'm infertile.
I trust this stack of
medical reports over
a single examination,
even from Dr. Ramirez.
Unfortunately, so do I.
Great.
Well, I'm...  sorry.
I'd better go.
Gina, wait.
Stay here, Walt.
I have an important announcement
to share with all of you.
I am retiring,
And I will announce my successor.
An hour ago, I had a
different plan, but now
everything has changed.
Henry.